Friends, in today's video I
must watch airtelxtream.in, let's start the video,
friends, you know that
there are three prepaid plans 239, 399 and 969,
with these three prepaid plans you are being
provided accidental insurance and
Airtel's end condition has given that
if you recharge any of these three plans, then
your personal
details along with your residence
address etc. will be
shared mainly with ICI, so that it becomes
very easy for you to get insurance coverage
here, friends, first of all let's talk about
what benefits you get with these three plans, first of all let's
talk about the plan of ₹
because in this particular plan,
here you get 28 days validity
with unlimited calls 100 times a day, along with that
you get a total of 2GB data,
4G data  You get 2GB, there is no unlimited 5G
data, it is being provided along with it.
See, the validity of the plan is
28 days, but here the
validity of the insurance has been kept for full 30 days.
Second, if I talk about the
399 plan, where you get 28
days validity with unlimited calls,
100 messages daily, you are being provided 2GB of high
speed 4G data, unlimited 5G data and other
benefits.
And here also the same thing is there,
death insurance up to ₹1 lakh and hospitalization insurance of ₹25000 will be
provided to you here. And
if I talk about the last plan, it is the 969
plan. Now in this plan, you
get 84 days validity, along with unlimited
calls, 100 SMS daily, you are being
provided 1.5GB of high speed data.
And here  You are also being provided insurance for 90 days.
If something happens during this time span,
you can directly go to
airtelxtream.in if you have multiple
airtelxtream.in